Okay, this one's rare.
This one is medium well.
Now go, go, go!
Hey, Phoebe!
Hey!
Hey, how was dinner?!
Dinner was good!
Just saying hi!
Now I'm going to go!
Oh. Well, hello there.
Hi.
I didn't see this
on the menu.
Oh, uh, Tim
this is Phoebe,
Phoebe, this is Tim
my new sous-chef.
Oh, so your Monica's boss?
Actually, she's my boss.
"Sous" is French for "under."
Ah! I sous-stand.
Hey, Tim.
I need a calamari
and a Caesar salad
and could you
give me the pesto?
Yeah.
You-you made pesto?
Yes, I did.
Would you say your pesto
is the best-o?
I don't know, but I would
say it's pretty good-o.
( laughing )
All right, I still need the
calamari and the Caesar salad.
I like your necklace.
Oh, I made it myself.
You are so talented.
Well, it's no pesto.
All right, all right, let's just
cut to the chase, okay?
You're single, you're single.
He gets off work at 11:00.
She'll be waiting
for your call.
I'll give him your number
if I could just get one
calamari and one Caesar salad!
I did not yell.
I am not putting
a dollar in the jar.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Wow, Bing.
Burning the midnight oil.
You know me, sir.
Oh, uh, I do have
a question for you.
Do you know how I can get around
the office computer network
so I can access
the really good Internet porn?
( laughing )
You're a joker, Bing.
What's funny about that?
Hey, sorry I kept
you waiting so long.
Hey, that's okay.
So, where do you want to go?
Oh, uh, I think you know
where I want to go.
The Hard Rock Cafe?
Yeah.
Again?
Yeah!
I'm telling you,
I like the food.
You like
the Purple Rain display.
Hey, Bob.
Hey, Toby, have
a good night.
Did that guy just call you Toby?
Yeah, he thinks
that's my name.
Well, why don't
you correct him?
Oh, it's been going
on way too long now.
I mean, the first
time he said it
we were just passing each
other in the hallway
so I didn't say anything
and then the
next time he said
"Hey, Toby, you
want a doughnut?"
and, I-I wanted
a doughnut.
And now it's
five years later
the doughnut's gone
and I'm still Toby.
Five years? Chandler,
you have to tell him.
No, that would be so awkward.
Look, besides, we work in
different departments.
He's on the sixth
floor, you know.
So he calls me Toby
once in a while.
What's the big deal?
Could be worse.
It's not like he's
calling me Muriel.
Muriel.
Why would he
call you Muriel?
Oh, my God.
Chandler M. Bing.
It's not just an "M."
Your middle name is Muriel!
Shh!
It is a family name.
Chandler Muriel Bing.
Boy, your parents never even
gave you a chance, did they?
Drake, I've discovered
the reason for all
your headaches
and memory loss.
What is it?
Apparently your brain transplant
was not entirely successful.
It seems your body
is rejecting Jessica's brain.
Is it serious?
Not if we extract tissue
from the original host body
synthesize antibodies, and
introduce them into your system
which could stop it
from rejecting the brain.
Well, that sounds
simple enough.
Let's just do that.
We would
but when we went to
exhume Jessica's body
it was gone.
DIRECTOR:
Cut! Very nice, people.
Okay, let me just get changed,
then we can go to dinner.
Well, what happened
to Jessica's body?
I'm not telling.
You'll have to see it on TV.
You don't know, do you?
No. Couldn't care less.
Hey, good scene, man.
Hey, you, too.
All right.
( clearing throat )
What? You weren't in it.
Oh!
Oh, sorry.
Uh, Cash,
this is my friend Rachel.
Rachel, Cash.
Cash, Rachel.
Hi.
So how come I haven't
seen you here before?
Well, Joey probably just
thinks I'll embarrass him.
He thinks I'm some kind
of a soap opera nut.
Which I'm not, I'm not.
( laughing )
Although, I do know
that your favorite ice cream
flavor is butter pecan
and, uh, and that
your dog's name is Wally.
Well, look at that,
I'm just stroking your arm.
Here we go! Here we go.
Oh, we're leaving.
Bye, Cash.
Bye.
Say hi to Wally.
Ooh, Monica.
Hi.
Oh, my God.
I had the best time
with Tim last night.
He is so sweet.
Oh, I can't wait to
get sous-neath him.
Uh...
I, I have to fire him.
But why?
Because he's
terrible. Okay?
He's slow,
he burns things.
Last night he lit
my pastry chef on fire.
Maybe he was just nervous.
You know, you can be
very intimidating.
Besides, I've
met your pastry chef
and she can stand to be
taken down a peg or two.
Well, now she
has no eyebrows.
Mission accomplished.
But Monica,
he loves his job so much.
Can't you just give him
another chance, please?
All right, but if he lights
someone else on fire
he is out of there!
That's fair.
Thank you so much. Thanks.
Oops. Looks like when
he got the pastry chef
he got you a little bit, too.
I paid to have this done.
Love it!
Hey.
Hi.
Oh, you know, Cash really
liked you the other day.
He said he thought
you were charming.
Oh, I thought
I was a complete idiot.
Hey, I'm with you.
He even asked me
if I thought you'd
go out with him.
Oh, Oh, I think I'm going
to throw up a little bit.
What did you say?
I said no.
What?!
I just figured
since you're pregnant
you're not going
to be seeing people.
Okay, Joey...
First of all
Cash Ford-- not people.
Second of all,
what did he say
when you told him
I was pregnant?
I didn't tell him.
I didn't know if you
were telling people.
This is back when I thought
Cash was still people.
Okay, don't tell him,
Just have him
call me, okay?
I really don't think
that's a great...
Okay, You go do it!
I'll come back
and meet more actors.
I'll meet them all!
Yup.
Hey, Bob.
Hey, how's my pal Toby
doing today?
If I see him, I'll ask.
Toby!
No, no, no, no, no.
Hey, hey, Bing.
Was that Bob from Six
you were just talking to?
Yeah, that was him.
Well, then you
know each other.
We're on a semi
first-name basis.
What do you think of
adding him to our team?
Bob?
Ooh. Working here with us?
Every day?
Yeah, I don't know
if he has what it takes.
Really?
They love him down on Six.
But this is 11.
It's almost twice
as hard up here.
Okay, I hear you
loud and clear.
Bob will stay put.
I think it's best, sir.
But we really do need to
find someone up here.
The work is starting
to pile up.
I've got a stack of documents
on my desk this high.
You know what
you should do?
Just toss them in the shredder
and claim you never got them.
( laughing )
That's a good one, Bing.
What does a guy have to do
to be taken seriously
around here?
Hey.
Okay, I gave him
another chance
but Tim has got to go.
But...
No. No, no.
He is totally incompetent.
Okay, I called the chef who
recommended him to me.
He said, "Ha, ha! Gotcha!"
Okay, okay, but
you can't fire him today.
Why not?
Because I'm
dumping him today.
What? You said he was so sweet.
He is sweet.
He's too sweet!
He calls me all the time.
"So, did you get home
from work okay?"
"Did you get out
of the shower okay?"
Well, just don't
pick up your phone.
Then he comes over.
"I'm so worried about you."
Ugh, be a man!
What? So now I'm
not allowed to fire him?
We can't fire him
and dump him in the same day.
He'll kill himself.
I'll fire him today
and you go out
with him for another week.
Are you kidding?
Another week with that simp,
I'll kill myself.
Okay, well, then
we'll both do it today
and he'll just have
to deal with it.
Okay, but the question is,
who's going to go first?
'Cause whoever goes second
is the bitch.
What do you mean?
Come on.
The boss that fires a guy
that's just been dumped? Bitch!
And the woman who dumps a guy
that's just been fired?
Blonde bitch!
I wanted to do this days ago
so I think I should go first.
Ugh, that makes sense.
Errgh, but...
Screw you, I'm going first!
Hey, Toby, you got a sec?
Sure, what's up?
I just had a meeting.
I was actually hoping
to get transferred up here
but I just found out
it's not going to happen.
Apparently somebody thinks
I'm not 11th floor material.
Say, uh...
Who the hell
is this Chandler?
Hey, what do you think
is a better excuse
for why I'm not drinking
on this date tonight--
I'm a recovering alcoholic
I'm a Mormon
or I got so hammered last night,
I'm still a little drunk?
Hey.
Hi.
So, what do you
want to do tonight?
There's a Ukrainian
film at the Angelica
that's supposed to be very
powerful. Interested?
No. No, but I'll go see
a normal-person movie with you.
Rach, you want to come?
Oh, no, I can't. I got a date.
A date?
Yeah. Why, is that
weird for you?
Why, no, it's
the opposite of weird.
It's, it's, uh, regular.
It's, it's uh... mundane.
It's, it's actually
a little dull.
It's no Ukrainian film,
I tell you.
Ooh, earrings!
A date?
She's got a date? With who?
I set her up
with this actor on my show.
You set her up?
No.
Joey, what were you thinking?
I was thinking that
it'd probably be okay
because Ross hasn't gone out
with Rachel in five years.
Joey, I'm not
worried about her.
I'm worried about my baby.
Whoever she dates,
my baby dates.
Now, now, where is this
"actor" taking them?
Hey! I'm an "actor" too.
I'm not sure. I think
they're taking the ferry
out to some Italian place
on Staten Island.
A ferry?
My baby is going on a ferry.
Do you have any idea how
dangerous those are?!
Aren't we talking about those
big boats that carry cars?
They go like
five miles an hour?
Why don't they just jump
out of an airplane, huh?
That's a fun date.
Or burn each other with matches.
That's fun, too. Woo!
( knocking )
Hey, Joey.
Hey, Cash.
Uh, hey, this is Ross.
Ross, this is Cash.
Hey.
I hear you're going
on a ferry tonight.
Yeah.
Bit of a daredevil, are we?
Hey, you guys.
Do you think this
is too slutty? Hi, Cash.
Hey, Rachel.
Hi.
Ready to go?
Yeah. All right,
I'll see you guys later.
Okay. Have
a great time, you guys.
Thank you.
Yes, it is too slutty!
Hi.
( gasps )
I'm so glad you called.
I feel like it's always
me calling you.
So, what's up?
Is everything okay
with Phoebe?
It will be, in a minute.
Listen-- Tim, you're
a really great guy.
That's because
I'm with you.
Aww.
I'm just, I'm in a place
in my life right now where I...
( loud beeping )
Oops. I'm so sorry.
This just in.
( laughing )
Oh, it's 911
from the restaurant.
That means Monica
needs me right away.
Oh, oh, no, she doesn't!
I know what that is;
you can stay.
Aww. I'll miss you,
too, Pheebs.
And I will be
holding you...
right here.
So, what movie
do you want to see?
And not another one
I have to read, okay?
I get enough of
that from books.
Books?
All right, car magazines,
cereal boxes...
but it's, like, enough!
Well, I'll tell you what,
why don't we, uh...
why don't we just stay here?
Let's not see a movie;
we'll just hang.
And just wait for Rachel
to come back from her date?
Hey, if that's what you want
to do, I'm not going to say no.
Dude, what is going on?
I just... I have to
find out how it went.
Why?
This guy could be
my baby's stepfather.
They go on one date
and you're worried about
them getting married?
He's not you!
I just... I...
I can't believe she's...
she's dating.
Well, Ross, what did you
think she was going to do?
I don't know.
I guess I just can't believe
any of this is happening.
Wh-What do you mean?
It's just that I always thought
when I had another kid,
it'd be different.
You know,
I-I love Ben
but every time I have to drop
him off at Carol and Susan's...
it's like, it breaks
my heart a little.
I mean, I-I've always had this
picture of me and my next wife
in bed on Sunday
and my kid comes running in
and leaps up onto the bed
and we all read the paper
together, you know?
Maybe fight over
the Science Section.
That's a nice picture.
Maybe you could
still have that.
No, no, I can't.
I mean, Rachel's out
with some guy.
My baby went with her.
Well, if anything, that picture
keeps moving further away.
Hey, can I ask you something?
In this... in this picture
of you and your wife...
is your wife Rachel?
It used to be.
Now-now she doesn't
really have a face.
Smokin' body, though.
Yeah, good call.
Yeah, but the face, Ross,
the face isn't Rachel.
No, but... aah, how much easier
would it be if it were.
Yeah, I know, but I don't
think that's what she wants.
No, it's not
what I want, either.
I mean, I can't force myself
to fall in love with her again.
Okay, Ross, maybe you
need a new picture. Okay?
It's not going to be what you
thought, but no matter what
there's going to be
a brand-new little baby.
Your baby.
Who cares what the
picture looks like.
Yeah.
Hey, tell
you what.
Let's you and me go out
and have some fun, huh?
Whatever you want. Come on.
We can still catch
that Ukrainian film.
No, I said fun.
Hey, Toby.
Hey, Bobby.
It's "Bob," actually.
Hey, you work up here.
Can you tell me where this
Chandler Bing's office is?
Uh... yeah.
Yeah, it's... it's
right-right-right down...
Yeah.
Right there.
Yeah. Let me ask you, why?
I want to talk to that bastard,
see what his problem is.
Okay, Bob, listen, uh...
I'm the reason you didn't
get the job up here.
Toby, don't.
Bob...
Toby, I'm not going to
let you cover for him.
Anything you say right now
will just get me more
upset with Chandler.
Well, that puts me
in a difficult position.
Hey.
I got your page.
Is everything okay?
Uh, well, th-that depends.
How are things with Phoebe?
Oh, it's great.
It's great.
Thank you so much
for introducing us.
Oh, my pleasure.
Okay, I'm afraid
I've got some bad news.
Phoebe!
Monica!
PHOEBE:
I'm...
I'm breaking
up with you!
You're fired!
What?
I'm-I'm breaking up with you.
You're fired.
Wh-Why?
I'm sorry, I'm just, I'm...
I'm just not ready
for a relationship right now.
An-And I'm sorry, too, but...
Well, I just, I like
things done a certain way
and the chemistry's
just not right.
Ooh, that's good.
The chemistry thing for us, too.
Wow.
Um, okay.
Um...
I-I-I-I realize
I came on a little strong
but it's only because
I think you're so amazing.
And, uh,
I-I just want to...
I want to tell you
how much I appreciate you
giving me an opportunity here
because I...
You're the most talented chef
I ever worked for.
Anyway...
Tim, wait.
Yeah?
Um...
I think I spoke too quickly.
Th-There's a learning curve
with this job, and...
maybe we could try it again.
Really?
Yeah.
Thank you so much, because
I know I can be better.
Okay.
And, Tim... I just want
to say good luck here.
Hello.
Hi.
( chuckles )
How was the date?
Well, I'm alone
and I just bought $15
worth of candy bars.
What do you think?
Uh-huh.
What happened?
Made the mistake of telling
him that I was pregnant.
Oh, he didn't, uh,
take it so well?
Well, better than you.
But, you know, still
not what you want.
Oh?
Yeah, he got all
weird and sputtery
and then he said, uh
"Yeah, I hear those
hemorrhoids are a bitch."
He sounds swell.
Doesn't he? Mm.
Hey, you want a...
you want a little cheering up?
Yes.
Sit down.
Okay.
Guess whose middle name
is Muriel.
( gasps )
Chandler M. Bing.
Yeah-uh.
Oh, my God.
( chortles )
Hmm...
I'm sorry about your date.
Aw, it's all right.
I guess I'm just done with
the whole dating thing.
It's just one more
thing in my life
that is suddenly
completely different.
This is hard.
Yeah, I know.
On the other hand, in, uh...
in about seven months
you're going to have something
that you're going to love
more than any guy
you've ever gone out with.
Just wait.
Wait until, uh...
Wait until the first time
your baby grabs your finger.
You have no idea.
Thanks, sweetie.
Mm-mm.
You, uh, you want
to grab some coffee?
Oh, no. I think
I'm going to go home
and eat ten candy bars.
Hey, I-I thought
I cheered you up.
Oh, you did--
there are 20 in here.
Right.
Good night.
Ross?
Yeah?
Hey, it's Mona.
From the wedding.
Oh, hi!
Hi.
Wow, uh... how are you?
I'm good, except, um,
you still owe me a dance.
Oh, that's
right.
Mm.
Well, uh, would you
be interested
in seeing a Ukrainian film?
( cracking up )
Oh, you're serious. Sure.
ROSS:
Great, well, um...
I-I think I might need
one more cup of coffee.
Sure. Let me get it for you.
Okay.
Bob.
Bob!
What the hell are you doing?!
I just found out
this is Chandler's office.
Come on, Toby, give me a hand.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]